<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Thai Boxing</string>

    <string name="navigation_drawer_open">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">Close navigation drawer</string>

    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="title_activity_history_menu">HistoryMenuActivity</string>
    <string name="title_activity_view_video">ViewVideoActivity</string>
    <string name="title_activity_view_video_data">ViewVideoDataActivity</string>
    <string name="title_activity_login_google_account">LoginGoogleAccountActivity</string>
    <string name="btn_logout_from_google">Logout from Google</string>
    <string name="btn_revoke_access">Revoke Access</string>
    <string name="title_activity_map">MapActivity</string>
    <string name="title_activity_scrolling_view_video">ScrollingViewVideoActivity</string>

    <string name="history_text">

        "   Muay Thai or Thai Boxing is the national sport and cultural martial art of Thailand. It was developed several hundreds of years ago as a form of close-combat that utilizes the entire body as a weapon.\n"
        "   Today its definitive origins are debated by modern scholars, as much of the muay thai history was lost when the Burmese ransacked Ayudhaya, Siam’s capital city in Thailand, during the 14th century.\n"
        "   Most written muya thai history was lost when the Burmese looted the temples and depositories of knowledge held in Ayudhaya, and what volumes were saved are now national treasures that are preserved and protected as documentation for Thai culture and heritage.\n\n"

    </string>

    <string name="history_text_two">

        "   History of Muay Thai and OriginMuay Thai is referred to as “The Art of Eight Limbs”  and using eight points of contact the body mimics weapons of war. The hands become the sword and dagger; the shins and forearms were hardened in training to act as armor against blows, and the elbow to fell opponents like a heavy mace or hammer  the legs and knees became the axe and staff. The body operated as one unit. The knees and elbows constantly searching and testing for an opening while grappling and trying to spin an enemy to the ground for the kill.\n"
        "   The King of Thailand is an avid fan of Muay Thai. Since being crowned its popularity has grown more than in any other era in history.\n\n"

    </string>
    <string name="title_activity_scrolling_history">ScrollingHistoryActivity</string>
    <string name="title_activity_scrolling_tiger_muay_thai">ScrollingTigerMuayThaiActivity</string>
    <string name="tiger_muay_thai_text">

        "   It all started with humble beginnings. wanting to help my head Muay Thai trainer,I bought a small one ring gym (that ring now sits in the advanced training area at Tiger Muay Thai and MMA) that we called Chalong Muay Thai. The website still exists. One ring and a few bags and I enjoyed coming from my job as Director of the English program at Darasamuth Catholic School near Central Mall and training in the afternoon. With just two trainers, some tires, a few bags, were far from the gym we are today, but you have to start somewhere.\n\n"

        "   Soon, people began to notice the the Muay Thai fighters and Thai flag we had painted on the building, and one day I show up and there are a couple people training. I didn’t mind, as my trainer would make some extra money and it as nice to have some others to work out with at the gym.\n\n"

        "   Few months later as high-season approached I found that each day there were regulars and more people showing up to train. We had added a trainer, and it was then I was approached by my future partners in an offer to open another gym in the area. Being that I had already trained at many gyms from Chiang Mai to Bangkok, Pattaya, and Phuket, I figured OK, lets do something bigger, but also better. It was then I also met our first trainer, now our gym manager, Phet Chaimanee.\n\n"

        "   Learning about partnerships: Lesson One. With three people as partners, often one partner is going to find himself outvoted in decisions about what or how to do something. In the end, one partner left seeing there would not be enough money for himself owning one-third of a gym and my other partner offered to sell his shares and pursue a business in boating and a Mexican restaurant, which I frequent visit to this day.\n\n"

        "   So I now find myself sole owner of Tiger Muay Thai and MMA training camp and he director of the English department at Phuket’s largest Catholic school. A choice had to be made. I had given nearly seven-years of my life to the school and church and was excited about creating something in Tiger Muay Thai and MMA Training Camp that would separate it from all the other gyms in Thailand: not just Muay thai training but MMA or Mixed Martial Arts which as a fight sport was becoming ever more popular.\n\n"

        "   It was tough times in the beginning as we went through several trainers until I finally met the man that would turn MMA Phuket’s training program around: Magical Ray Elbe.\n\n"

        "   So with hard work, determination, and a plan to be different in the way Muay Thai was being taught at the gyms I had trained, I decided that we would promote tradition, culture, respect, and sport for competitiveness. We would be a traditional camp that brought modern standards of training to the sport. Tiger Muay Thai would offer technique classes in a learn first and then practice plan. we would hire quality trainers from Bangkok and Northern Thailand, the heart of Muay Thai and teach Lumpinee style fighting; moving ahead, attacking your opponent and strong belief in conditioning. \n\n"

        "   Five-years later, Tiger Muay Thai has dozens of repeat guests that return every year, World Champion trainers from WMC, Lumpinee, Rajadamnoen, WBC, and Bangkok TV and a detailed, organized, and scheduled training plan that includes training programs for beginners, intermediate, and advanced Muay Thai and beginners and advanced MMA."
    </string>
    <string name="title_activity_main2">Main2Activity</string>
    <string name="title_activity_accessories">AccessoriesActivity</string>
    <string name="title_activity_review_image">ReviewImageActivity</string>
    <string name="title_activity_cart">CartActivity</string>
    <string name="title_activity_select_package">SelectPackageActivity</string>
    <string name="title_activity_scrolling_sport_equipment">ScrollingSportEquipmentActivity</string>
    <string name="large_text">
        "Material is the metaphor.\n\n"

        "A material metaphor is the unifying theory of a rationalized space and a system of motion."
        "The material is grounded in tactile reality, inspired by the study of paper and ink, yet "
        "technologically advanced and open to imagination and magic.\n"
        "Surfaces and edges of the material provide visual cues that are grounded in reality. The "
        "use of familiar tactile attributes helps users quickly understand affordances. Yet the "
        "flexibility of the material creates new affordances that supercede those in the physical "
        "world, without breaking the rules of physics.\n"
        "The fundamentals of light, surface, and movement are key to conveying how objects move, "
        "interact, and exist in space and in relation to each other. Realistic lighting shows "
        "seams, divides space, and indicates moving parts.\n\n"

        "Bold, graphic, intentional.\n\n"

        "The foundational elements of print based design typography, grids, space, scale, color, "
        "and use of imagery guide visual treatments. These elements do far more than please the "
        "eye. They create hierarchy, meaning, and focus. Deliberate color choices, edge to edge "
        "imagery, large scale typography, and intentional white space create a bold and graphic "
        "interface that immerse the user in the experience.\n"
        "An emphasis on user actions makes core functionality immediately apparent and provides "
        "waypoints for the user.\n\n"

        "Motion provides meaning.\n\n"

        "Motion respects and reinforces the user as the prime mover. Primary user actions are "
        "inflection points that initiate motion, transforming the whole design.\n"
        "All action takes place in a single environment. Objects are presented to the user without "
        "breaking the continuity of experience even as they transform and reorganize.\n"
        "Motion is meaningful and appropriate, serving to focus attention and maintain continuity. "
        "Feedback is subtle yet clear. Transitions are efﬁcient yet coherent.\n\n"

        "3D world.\n\n"

        "The material environment is a 3D space, which means all objects have x, y, and z "
        "dimensions. The z-axis is perpendicularly aligned to the plane of the display, with the "
        "positive z-axis extending towards the viewer. Every sheet of material occupies a single "
        "position along the z-axis and has a standard 1dp thickness.\n"
        "On the web, the z-axis is used for layering and not for perspective. The 3D world is "
        "emulated by manipulating the y-axis.\n\n"

        "Light and shadow.\n\n"

        "Within the material environment, virtual lights illuminate the scene. Key lights create "
        "directional shadows, while ambient light creates soft shadows from all angles.\n"
        "Shadows in the material environment are cast by these two light sources. In Android "
        "development, shadows occur when light sources are blocked by sheets of material at "
        "various positions along the z-axis. On the web, shadows are depicted by manipulating the "
        "y-axis only. The following example shows the card with a height of 6dp.\n\n"

        "Resting elevation.\n\n"

        "All material objects, regardless of size, have a resting elevation, or default elevation "
        "that does not change. If an object changes elevation, it should return to its resting "
        "elevation as soon as possible.\n\n"

        "Component elevations.\n\n"

        "The resting elevation for a component type is consistent across apps (e.g., FAB elevation "
        "does not vary from 6dp in one app to 16dp in another app).\n"
        "Components may have different resting elevations across platforms, depending on the depth "
        "of the environment (e.g., TV has a greater depth than mobile or desktop).\n\n"

        "Responsive elevation and dynamic elevation offsets.\n\n"

        "Some component types have responsive elevation, meaning they change elevation in response "
        "to user input (e.g., normal, focused, and pressed) or system events. These elevation "
        "changes are consistently implemented using dynamic elevation offsets.\n"
        "Dynamic elevation offsets are the goal elevation that a component moves towards, relative "
        "to the component’s resting state. They ensure that elevation changes are consistent "
        "across actions and component types. For example, all components that lift on press have "
        "the same elevation change relative to their resting elevation.\n"
        "Once the input event is completed or cancelled, the component will return to its resting "
        "elevation.\n\n"

        "Avoiding elevation interference.\n\n"

        "Components with responsive elevations may encounter other components as they move between "
        "their resting elevations and dynamic elevation offsets. Because material cannot pass "
        "through other material, components avoid interfering with one another any number of ways, "
        "whether on a per component basis or using the entire app layout.\n"
        "On a component level, components can move or be removed before they cause interference. "
        "For example, a floating action button (FAB) can disappear or move off screen before a "
        "user picks up a card, or it can move if a snackbar appears.\n"
        "On the layout level, design your app layout to minimize opportunities for interference. "
        "For example, position the FAB to one side of stream of a cards so the FAB won’t interfere "
        "when a user tries to pick up one of cards.\n\n"
    </string>
    <string name="title_activity_scrolling_upper_part">ScrollingUpperPartActivity</string>
    <string name="title_activity_show_skill">ShowSkillActivity</string>
    <string name="title_activity_set_time">SetTimeActivity</string>
</resources>
